<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Technosonic2k17</string>

    <string name="trtime">Time : 10:30AM</string>
    <string name="trtitle">TRUSS BRIDGE MODELLING</string>
    <string name="tv1">Details:</string>
    <string name="tv2">The task assigned to the participating teams is to design and
        construct a bridge model, which meets the criteria as given in the rules link.
        The thinking ability and on the spot decision making ability will be tested by
        this competition</string>
    <string name="tv3">Description:</string>
    <string name="tv4">The bridge model should span a total length of 120.0 cm.
The truss and the roadway must be constructed in a single span
and brought to the venue.</string>
    <string name="tv5">Bridge model Construction Criteria</string>
    <string name="tv6"> All parts of the bridge model must be built with Popsicle
sticks (120mm x 12mm x 2mm) and
 “Fevicol MR” (No other material is acceptable and team will be
disqualified if used).
 The roadway (deck slab) must span a total length of 120.0 cm ±
0.5 cm with the centre of the bridge model resting on the support
(which will be
Provided).
 The width of the bridge model must not exceed 15.0 cm at any
point and must be more than 10.0 cm at every point.
 The total thickness of the roadway/ deck slab (mandatory toconstruct in model) must not be more
        than 0.3 cm.
 A roadway / deck slab is required for all bridge models.
 Overlap of two parallel members along their length is not allowed.
 Piers must not be constructed.
 The total weight of the bridge model must not exceed 0.750 kg.
 Coating of paint, adhesive, polish, or any other material must
not be applied to exposed surfaces of the bridge model</string>
    <string name="tv7">Testing Criteria</string>
    <string name="tv8">
Participants have to prepare a TRUSS BRIDGE as per defined
criteria.
 Initial load applied would be 1.5 Kg. Bridge model
should sustain minimum load otherwise it will be
disqualified.
 The bridge model shall be loaded on both ends of the bridge model
(50.0 cm
from the centre of the bridge model on both sides)

If for any reason the loading system cannot be placed at the point
specified, the loading mechanism will be moved towards the ends
of the bridge model until a suitable point is found for loading.
.

Measurement shall stop after peak load is reached, or a deflection
greater than 3.0 cm is reached at any point.
 Winner will be decided by the judges.
 Decision of judges will be final and no further debate will be
allowed.
Some rules and penalties may be mentioned on the spot.
Penalty Criteria
• If bridge model’s total span is less than defined, the model will be
penalized/ disqualified.*
• Use of any material other than specified will result in
disqualification.
• Bridge models with weight greater than specified will be
penalized/ disqualified.*
• If bridge model’s width is greater or smaller than defined, the
model will be penalized/ disqualified.*
• Any irregular cross-sections or irregularities in the workmanship,
bent bridge models, designs, etc. that do not allow us to test the
bridge model on the stated loading mechanism will result in
penalty/ disqualification.*
• Bridge models with piers will be disqualified.
• If coating of paint, adhesive, polish, or any other material is
applied to any exposed surface of the bridge model, the model
will be disqualified.</string>
    <string name="tv10">**Penalties will be declared at the time of competition. Penalties will be
decided by the judges.</string>
    <string name="tv11">Winning Price:</string>
    <string name="tv12">1st 1500/-
2nd 1000/-</string>
    <string name="tv13">Student Coordinator:</string>
    <string name="tv14">Suketu Patel
(7046408353)</string>


</resources>
